<contract>
    <parties>
        <party>
            <name>Equitable Financial Life Insurance Company</name>
            <type>Corporation</type>
            <capacity>Party</capacity>
            <address>1290 Avenue of the Americas, New York, New York, 10104</address>
        </party>
        <party>
            <name>Equitable Distributors, LLC</name>
            <type>Limited Liability Company</type>
            <capacity>Party</capacity>
            <address>1290 Avenue of the Americas, New York, New York, 10104</address>
        </party>
    </parties>
    <offerAndAcceptance>
        <offer>The provision of personnel, property, and services in accordance with specified terms and conditions.</offer>
        <acceptance>The parties agree to enter into this Amended and Restated Agreement.</acceptance>
        <meetingOfMinds>The effective date of the Agreement is November 1, 2023.</meetingOfMinds>
    </offerAndAcceptance>
    <consideration>
        <description>Equitable Distributors shall reimburse Equitable Financial for costs incurred.</description>
        <value>Based on direct and indirect costs as specified in the Agreement.</value>
    </consideration>
    <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>Both parties intend to create legal relations.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
    <legalityOfPurpose>The purpose of the Agreement is lawful under applicable laws.</legalityOfPurpose>
    <certaintyOfTerms>
        <subjectMatter>Provision of services including management and administrative functions.</subjectMatter>
        <price>Costs based on actual expenses incurred.</price>
        <timeForPerformance>The term commences on the Effective Date and continues until terminated.</timeForPerformance>
    </certaintyOfTerms>
    <consent>Both parties consent to the terms and conditions outlined in this Agreement.</consent>
    <formAndFormalities>Agreement is signed and executed in counterparts.</formAndFormalities>
    <durationAndTermination>
        <duration>Until terminated by either party with 90 days’ written notice.</duration>
        <terminationConditions>The termination conditions are specified within the Agreement.</terminationConditions>
        <renewalTerms>No specified renewal terms; termination can occur at will.</renewalTerms>
    </durationAndTermination>
    <representationsAndWarranties>Both parties agree to confidentiality and compliance with applicable laws.</representationsAndWarranties>
    <indemnification>No specific indemnification clause provided.</indemnification>
    <disputeResolution>
        <method>Arbitration according to the rules of the American Arbitration Association.</method>
        <details>Arbitration to take place in New York, New York.</details>
    </disputeResolution>
    <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
        <governingLaw>State of New York</governingLaw>
        <jurisdiction>New York, New York</jurisdiction>
    </governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <severability>Should any provision be found invalid, the remaining provisions shall remain in effect.</severability>
    <forceMajeure>No explicit force majeure clause noted.</forceMajeure>
    <confidentiality>Both parties agree to preserve the confidentiality of shared customer information.</confidentiality>
    <assignmentAndDelegation>No assignment shall take effect without prior written consent from the other party.</assignmentAndDelegation>
    <signatures>
        <signature>
            <partyName>Equitable Financial Life Insurance Company</partyName>
            <dateSigned>2023-11-01</dateSigned>
            <declaration>By: Robin M. Raju, Chief Financial Officer</declaration>
        </signature>
        <signature>
            <partyName>Equitable Distributors, LLC</partyName>
            <dateSigned>2023-11-01</dateSigned>
            <declaration>By: Nick Lane, President</declaration>
        </signature>
    </signatures>
</contract>