<contract>
  <parties>
    <party>
      <name>Party A (company name)</name>
      <type>Company</type>
      <capacity>Employer</capacity>
      <address>Address</address>
    </party>
    <party>
      <name>Party B (employee name)</name>
      <type>Individual</type>
      <capacity>Employee</capacity>
      <address>Address</address>
    </party>
  </parties>
  
  <offerAndAcceptance>
    <offer>The Labor Contract is formulated in accordance with the Labor Law of the People’s Republic of China and relevant laws and regulations.</offer>
    <acceptance>The Contract shall take effect from the date of confirmation by both parties.</acceptance>
    <meetingOfMinds>Both parties agree based on principles of equality, voluntariness, legality, fairness, honesty, and credibility.</meetingOfMinds>
  </offerAndAcceptance>
  
  <consideration>
    <description>Employment remuneration for Party B.</description>
    <value>Monthly wage as per the Offer Letter or wage confirmation agreement.</value>
  </consideration>
  
  <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>This contract established by Party A and Party B creates legal relations binding on both parties.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
  
  <legalityOfPurpose>The Contract is lawful and complies with national laws and regulations.</legalityOfPurpose>
  
  <certaintyOfTerms>
    <subjectMatter>Terms of employment, including working hours, duties, and remuneration.</subjectMatter>
    <price>Monthly wage determined by negotiations and agreements.</price>
    <timeForPerformance>Contract duration and probation period are specified herein.</timeForPerformance>
  </certaintyOfTerms>
  
  <consent>Party B consents to work and adhere to the terms set forth within the Contract.</consent>
    
  <formAndFormalities>The Contract is signed through an electronic signing platform.</formAndFormalities>
  
  <durationAndTermination>
    <duration>Fixed-term labor contract.</duration>
    <terminationConditions>Contract termination upon expiration or mutual agreement.</terminationConditions>
    <renewalTerms>Possible renewal upon expiration with mutual agreement.</renewalTerms>
  </durationAndTermination>
  
  <representationsAndWarranties>Both parties warrant the truthfulness of the information provided regarding their identities and capabilities.</representationsAndWarranties>
  
  <indemnification>Party B will indemnify Party A against any losses arising from misrepresentation.</indemnification>
  
  <disputeResolution>
    <method>Negotiation and arbitration through local labor dispute arbitration committee.</method>
    <details>Should negotiation fail, arbitration will be pursued according to the Labor Dispute Mediation and Arbitration Law.</details>
  </disputeResolution>

  <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <governingLaw>Chinese laws and regulations.</governingLaw>
    <jurisdiction>People’s court where Party A is located.</jurisdiction>
  </governingLawAndJurisdiction>

  <severability>If any provision is invalid, the rest of the Contract shall remain effective.</severability>
  
  <forceMajeure>No specific mention in the contract text.</forceMajeure>
  
  <confidentiality>Party B shall maintain confidentiality of Party A's trade secrets as per the Confidentiality Agreement.</confidentiality>
  
  <assignmentAndDelegation>Neither party can assign their rights or obligations without consent from the other.</assignmentAndDelegation>
  
  <signatures>
    <signature>
      <partyName>Party A</partyName>
      <dateSigned>DD/MM/YY</dateSigned>
      <declaration>Party A agrees to the Contract.</declaration>
    </signature>
    <signature>
      <partyName>Party B</partyName>
      <dateSigned>DD/MM/YY</dateSigned>
      <declaration>Party B agrees to the terms of the Contract.</declaration>
    </signature>
  </signatures>
</contract>