<contract>
  <parties>
    <party>
      <name>Brightcast LLC</name>
      <type>LLC</type>
      <capacity>Media Buyer</capacity>
      <address>2699 Pacific Coast Highway, Suite 200, Hermosa Beach, CA 90254</address>
    </party>
    <party>
      <name>Eva Live Inc</name>
      <type>Corporation</type>
      <capacity>Company</capacity>
    </party>
  </parties>
  <offerAndAcceptance>
    <offer>BRIGHTCAST wishes to engage Company to provide the Services set out herein.</offer>
    <acceptance>Company agrees to provide the Services as described.</acceptance>
    <meetingOfMinds>The parties agree upon terms regarding services and payment.</meetingOfMinds>
  </offerAndAcceptance>
  <consideration>
    <description>Revenue generated from ad spends.</description>
    <value>85% of Paid Search Revenues.</value>
  </consideration>
  <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>Yes, both parties intend to be legally bound by the Agreement.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
  <legalityOfPurpose>The purpose is to engage in media buying services legally.</legalityOfPurpose>
  <certaintyOfTerms>
    <subjectMatter>Media buying services as described in the contract.</subjectMatter>
    <price>Fees calculated as 85% of revenues.</price>
    <timeForPerformance>Upon acceptance of the agreement until terminated by either party.</timeForPerformance>
  </certaintyOfTerms>
  <consent>Both parties mutually consent to the terms outlined in the Agreement.</consent>
  <formAndFormalities>Agreement is in writing and signed by both parties.</formAndFormalities>
  <durationAndTermination>
    <duration>Indefinite until terminated by either party with 30 days' notice.</duration>
    <terminationConditions>Either party can terminate without cause with written notice.</terminationConditions>
  </durationAndTermination>
  <representationsAndWarranties>BRIGHTCAST represents it owns the necessary intellectual property for the platform.</representationsAndWarranties>
  <indemnification>Each party indemnifies the other from claims resulting from their acts or omissions.</indemnification>
  <disputeResolution>
    <method>Negotiation followed by mediation if unresolved.</method>
    <details>Parties will designate representatives to resolve disputes informally.</details>
  </disputeResolution>
  <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <governingLaw>California</governingLaw>
    <jurisdiction>State courts of California.</jurisdiction>
  </governingLawAndJurisdiction>
  <severability>If any provision is found unenforceable, the remaining provisions remain in force.</severability>
  <forceMajeure>Neither party is liable for delays due to causes beyond their control.</forceMajeure>
  <confidentiality>Both parties agree to maintain confidentiality of proprietary information.</confidentiality>
  <assignmentAndDelegation>Neither party may assign obligations without the prior written consent of the other.</assignmentAndDelegation>
  <signatures>
    <signature>
      <partyName>Brightcast LLC</partyName>
      <dateSigned>2022-05-05</dateSigned>
      <declaration>Signed by authorized representative.</declaration>
    </signature>
    <signature>
      <partyName>Eva Live Inc</partyName>
      <dateSigned>2022-05-16</dateSigned>
      <declaration>Signed by Phil Aspin, Director.</declaration>
    </signature>
  </signatures>
</contract>