<contract>
    <parties>
      <party>
        <name>NGO/UN agency</name>
        <type>First Party</type>
        <capacity>non-profit humanitarian organization</capacity>
        <address>[Address]</address>
      </party>
      <party>
        <name>Company/agent</name>
        <type>Second Party</type>
        <capacity>financial service provider</capacity>
        <address>[Address]</address>
      </party>
    </parties>
    <offerAndAcceptance>
      <offer>The First Party desires to transfer money from Turkey into Syria for humanitarian activities.</offer>
      <acceptance>The Second Party agrees to facilitate the transfers.</acceptance>
      <meetingOfMinds>Both parties agree to collaborate on the humanitarian effort.</meetingOfMinds>
    </offerAndAcceptance>
    <consideration>
      <description>The consideration for this Contract shall be the transfer of money for humanitarian assistance.</description>
      <value>Valued in USD or Euro based on a pre-agreed exchange rate.</value>
    </consideration>
    <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>The parties intend to create a legal contract.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
    <legalityOfPurpose>The purpose of this agreement is legal under applicable laws.</legalityOfPurpose>
    <certaintyOfTerms>
      <subjectMatter>Money transfer for humanitarian aid.</subjectMatter>
      <price>To be determined based on exchange rate.</price>
      <timeForPerformance>This contract is valid for a period of ______ months from the signature date.</timeForPerformance>
    </certaintyOfTerms>
    <consent>Both parties consent to the terms outlined in this Contract.</consent>
    <formAndFormalities>Both parties agree to sign this Contract.</formAndFormalities>
    <durationAndTermination>
      <duration>_______ months.</duration>
      <terminationConditions>Two weeks written notice required for termination.</terminationConditions>
      <renewalTerms>To be mutually agreed upon.</renewalTerms>
    </durationAndTermination>
    <representationsAndWarranties>Both parties represent that they have the capacity to enter into this Contract.</representationsAndWarranties>
    <indemnification>The Second Party agrees to indemnify the First Party for any failure to perform as required by this agreement.</indemnification>
    <disputeResolution>
      <method>Mediation</method>
      <details>Disputes not resolved amicably will be taken to a mutually agreed mediator on a cost-sharing basis.</details>
    </disputeResolution>
    <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
      <governingLaw>Applicable law in the jurisdiction where the First Party is registered.</governingLaw>
      <jurisdiction>Exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in the location of the First Party.</jurisdiction>
    </governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <severability>If any part of this agreement is found to be unenforceable, the remaining sections will remain in effect.</severability>
    <forceMajeure>Neither party will be liable for delays caused by circumstances beyond their control.</forceMajeure>
    <confidentiality>All information exchanged shall be kept confidential by both parties.</confidentiality>
    <assignmentAndDelegation>Neither party may assign or delegate their obligations under this Contract without prior written consent of the other party.</assignmentAndDelegation>
    <signatures>
      <signature>
        <partyName>NGO/UN agency</partyName>
        <dateSigned>______-__-__</dateSigned>
        <declaration>I, representative of the First Party, agree to the terms of this contract.</declaration>
      </signature>
      <signature>
        <partyName>Company/agent</partyName>
        <dateSigned>______-__-__</dateSigned>
        <declaration>I, representative of the Second Party, agree to the terms of this contract.</declaration>
      </signature>
    </signatures>
  </contract>