<contract>
    <parties>
        <party>
            <name>SANTA CRUZ COUNTY REGIONAL TRANSPORTATION COMMISSION</name>
            <type>Commission</type>
            <capacity>Public Authority</capacity>
            <address>Santa Cruz County Regional Transportation Commission, 1523 Pacific Ave, Santa Cruz, CA 95060</address>
        </party>
        <party>
            <name>CONSULTANT</name>
            <type>Consultant</type>
            <capacity>Professional Service Provider</capacity>
            <address>________ (Address not provided)</address>
        </party>
    </parties>
    <offerAndAcceptance>
        <offer>This Agreement serves as a Professional Services Agreement for specific services or projects as referenced in the contract.</offer>
        <acceptance>Both parties acknowledge and consent to the terms and conditions as outlined herein.</acceptance>
        <meetingOfMinds>The parties have reached a mutual understanding and agreement of the terms laid out in this document.</meetingOfMinds>
    </offerAndAcceptance>
    <consideration>
        <description>Payment for professional services rendered by the CONSULTANT.</description>
        <value>Not to exceed $_____ for time and materials as per Exhibit B - Fee Schedule.</value>
    </consideration>
    <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>Both parties intend for this Agreement to create legal obligations.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
    <legalityOfPurpose>The purpose of this Agreement complies with all applicable laws and regulations.</legalityOfPurpose>
    <certaintyOfTerms>
        <subjectMatter>Scope of Services as laid out in Exhibit A.</subjectMatter>
        <price>Not to exceed $_____.</price>
        <timeForPerformance>This Agreement shall commence upon approval and notification to proceed.</timeForPerformance>
    </certaintyOfTerms>
    <consent>CONSULTANT shall obtain written consent for any changes to key personnel as specified.</consent>
    <formAndFormalities>This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties and is binding upon execution.</formAndFormalities>
    <durationAndTermination>
        <duration>This Agreement shall take effect on (DATE) and end on (DATE).</duration>
        <terminationConditions>Termination by either party with a written notice as specified.</terminationConditions>
        <renewalTerms>Renewal shall be documented by written agreement from both parties.</renewalTerms>
    </durationAndTermination>
    <representationsAndWarranties>Each party represents that they have the authority to enter into this Agreement.</representationsAndWarranties>
    <indemnification>CONSULTANT shall indemnify and hold harmless COMMISSION from any claims arising from negligence.</indemnification>
    <disputeResolution>
        <method>Dispute resolution via a committee of the COMMISSION's Contract Manager and Executive Director.</method>
        <details>Unresolved disputes may be reviewed by the COMMISSION GOVERNING BOARD.</details>
    </disputeResolution>
    <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
        <governingLaw>State of California</governingLaw>
        <jurisdiction>Jurisdiction in the courts in California.</jurisdiction>
    </governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <severability>If any provision is found to be invalid, the remainder will still be enforceable.</severability>
    <forceMajeure>Neither party shall be liable for failure to perform due to unforeseen circumstances.</forceMajeure>
    <confidentiality>All proprietary information obtained during this Agreement shall remain confidential.</confidentiality>
    <assignmentAndDelegation>CONSULTANT cannot assign this Agreement without prior written consent from COMMISSION.</assignmentAndDelegation>
    <signatures>
        <signature>
            <partyName>CONSULTANT</partyName>
            <dateSigned>_______ (Date not provided)</dateSigned>
            <declaration>This Agreement is executed by the duly authorized representatives.</declaration>
        </signature>
        <signature>
            <partyName>SANTA CRUZ COUNTY REGIONAL TRANSPORTATION COMMISSION</partyName>
            <dateSigned>_______ (Date not provided)</dateSigned>
            <declaration>This Agreement is executed by the duly authorized representatives.</declaration>
        </signature>
    </signatures>
</contract>