<contract>
    <parties>
        <party>
            <name>Alkermes, INC.</name>
            <type>Corporation</type>
            <capacity>Provider</capacity>
            <address>900 Winter Street, Waltham, Massachusetts 02451</address>
        </party>
        <party>
            <name>Mural Oncology, Inc.</name>
            <type>Corporation</type>
            <capacity>Receiver</capacity>
            <address>852 Winter Street, Waltham, Massachusetts 02451</address>
        </party>
    </parties>
    <offerAndAcceptance>
        <offer>Alkermes US offers transition services to Mural US.</offer>
        <acceptance>Mural US accepts to obtain the services as set forth in this Agreement.</acceptance>
        <meetingOfMinds>The parties agree on terms for services necessary for the transition after the separation agreement.</meetingOfMinds>
    </offerAndAcceptance>
    <consideration>
        <description>Provision of transition services as per Schedule.</description>
        <value>Fees as set forth in the Transition Service Schedule.</value>
    </consideration>
    <intentionToCreateLegalRelations>This Agreement creates legal obligations between the Parties.</intentionToCreateLegalRelations>
    <legalityOfPurpose>The purpose of the Agreement is legal and enforceable.</legalityOfPurpose>
    <certaintyOfTerms>
        <subjectMatter>Transition services related to the Oncology Business.</subjectMatter>
        <price>Fees as set forth in the Transition Service Schedule.</price>
        <timeForPerformance>The term is defined in the Agreement, terminable with written notice.</timeForPerformance>
    </certaintyOfTerms>
    <consent>The parties grant consent for the specified services and cooperation.</consent>
    <formAndFormalities>Written agreements are required for any amendments.</formAndFormalities>
    <durationAndTermination>
        <duration>Starting from November 13, 2023, until services are rendered as per schedule or extended.</duration>
        <terminationConditions>Termination can occur due to breach or material failure.</terminationConditions>
        <renewalTerms>May renew for an additional period based on mutual agreement.</renewalTerms>
    </durationAndTermination>
    <representationsAndWarranties>The parties represent they have authority to enter into this Agreement.</representationsAndWarranties>
    <indemnification>The parties agree to indemnify each other based on the specified terms.</indemnification>
    <disputeResolution>
        <method>Negotiations followed by arbitration if unresolved.</method>
        <details>Disputes must be notified and resolved within a specified timeframe.</details>
    </disputeResolution>
    <governingLawAndJurisdiction>
        <governingLaw>State of Delaware</governingLaw>
        <jurisdiction>Delaware Court of Chancery</jurisdiction>
    </governingLawAndJurisdiction>
    <severability>If any provision is invalid, the remaining provisions remain in effect.</severability>
    <forceMajeure>No liability for delays caused by external force majeure events.</forceMajeure>
    <confidentiality>Parties to maintain confidentiality regarding sensitive information.</confidentiality>
    <assignmentAndDelegation>Assignment requires mutual consent unless specified otherwise.</assignmentAndDelegation>
    <signatures>
        <signature>
            <partyName>Alkermes, INC.</partyName>
            <dateSigned>2023-11-13</dateSigned>
            <declaration>This Agreement is accepted and duly executed.</declaration>
        </signature>
        <signature>
            <partyName>Mural Oncology, Inc.</partyName>
            <dateSigned>2023-11-13</dateSigned>
            <declaration>This Agreement is accepted and duly executed.</declaration>
        </signature>
    </signatures>
</contract>